adicate.com 2010-02-13

# Time Ads|Privacy Policy|Advertik Time Advertising

**Privacy Policy for Advertik**

Please read this policy to understand what information Advertik collects, how the information is used, and what choices you have regarding collection and use of your information when using Advertik. **Policy Scope**  
This policy covers information you share, both personally identifiable and non-identifiable information, with Advertik as a visitor to the Advertik web site.  If you are a business enrolled in the Advertik online program, then you are subject to the Advertik Terms and Conditions.  Please refer to the Advertik Terms and Conditions for more information if this pertains to you. **Information We Collect**  
Advertik collects both personally identifiable information as well as non-personally identifiable information. **Personally Identifiable Information**  
Personally identifiable information is any information that identifies a specific individual, such as a name, email address, or phone number. 

Advertik only collects personally identifiable information if that information is voluntarily provided by the user. 

This may happen in several ways:

  * Contact Us.  If a user submits a query or comment to Advertik via the Contact Us function, personally identifiable information may be collected in order for Advertik to respond to the user. 

  * Message Board.  A user may submit personally identifiable information in the process of registering or posting a message on the Advertik message boards. 

  * Subscription.  A user may subscribe to periodic updates from Advertik and provide an email address and/or name. 

  * IP Address Logging.  Advertik collects users’ IP addresses in its log files. Your IP address may be logged and recorded. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
Non-personally identifiable information is any information about the user that does not uniquely identify the individual.  
Advertik collects non-personally identifiable information in several ways:

  * Log files.  A user’s activities on the Advertik web site are logged. Clickstream information about the user is captured. 

  * Cookies.  A cookie may be stored on the user’s computer to indicate activity during a user’s session as well as activity across sessions. 

  * Clear Pixels.  Clear pixels (also called beacons) may be used to track the activity and flow of a user on the Advertik web site. 

  * Demographic Data.  Demographic data, including but not limited to age range, sex, and geography may be recorded. 

**Information Use**  
Advertik uses the personally identifiable information you share with us to respond to your query, comment, or request for a subscription.  Personally identifiable information you share with us for the purpose of Message Board use is used to manage your account and to uniquely identify your posts for other users of the Message Boards.

Advertik uses the non-personally identifiable information to track the performance of the Advertik web site, analyze the performance, and improve it for your benefit.

All information may be used for additional purposes, such as auditing, research, and development of additional web site capabilities or services.

Information Sharing  
Advertik does not rent, share, or sell the personally identifiable information you share with us without your prior permission.

Non-personally identifiable information may be shared with 3rd party providers, in aggregated or unaggregated fashion. 

Please note that we may also share information in the event that we are asked to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, or as otherwise permitted by law.

If and when we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

Advertik may transfer the information it collects to any successor in interest to Advertik (such as a company that acquires Advertik), or internally to one or more affiliates (such as a corporate subsidiary or parent).

 **Acceptance of Privacy Policy**  
When you use the Advertik web site, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and Advertik will have the right to use your information as described in the Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy, you must immediately discontinue use of the Advertik web site.  Advertik reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time.  Your continued use of the Advertik web site after a change in the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of those changes. **Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Advertik at [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy20873%20=%20'support'%20+%20'@';%20addy20873%20=%20addy20873%20+%20'pubmatic'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy20873%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy20873%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)[support@Advertik.com](mailto:support@Advertik.com) .
